Southwest Neighborhood Assembly Collection 1997.010
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Southwest Neighborhood Assembly Collection
1963-2011
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Southwest Neighborhood Assembly (Washington, D.C.)
1997.010
7 Linear feet
Neighborhood associations
- Before 1963 Binder - Org Records (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1963 - Early Records of SWNA binder (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1964 - General Documents binder (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1965 - General Documents and Org Records binder (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bylaws Binder, 1967 - 2008 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Annual Reports Binder, 1995 - 2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bylaws, Reports, Meeting Minutes Binder, 1984 - 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bylaws, Reports, Meeting Minutes Binder, 1995 - 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Minutes and Other Records Binder, 1998 (compiled 2006) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Annual Reports Folder, 1998 - 2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Meeting Minutes, Agendas Binder, 2007 - 2008 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Articles, Grant Program Materials Folder, 2002 - 2003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Call box project materials, 2000 - 2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Call box project materials and ADA documents folder (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Minutes, letters, emails, Heritage Trail, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Budget and Expense Reports, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Meeting Agenda, Board Members List, By-Laws Binder, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Meeting Minutes Binder, 2005-2006 (April to March) (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Call Box Materials, Waterside Mall and Towers, 11th Street Bridge Project, Minutes folder, August - December, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Compact Disc "History of Old SW," Budget Meetings, Anacostia Waterfront, Walking Tour, and Neighborhood History, folder, January - July 2006 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Redevelopment documents, urban renewal, Call Boxes, Dupont Circle Call Box Art, Fundraising, Baseball Stadium folder, May - December 2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Call Box materials, grant application, Waterside Towers Petition to save businesses folder, January - April 2005 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Art on Call Call Box Project, Call Box Correspondence, Committee Task Force Reports folder, January - March 2005 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Call Boxes map and related materials, meeting agendas and minutes, Cherry Blossom Festival, April - December 2008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Call Box Correspondence, Annual Reports, Cherry Blossom Festival folder, 2008-03-01 00:00:00 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Call Box Materials--articles and letters, Washington Studies Conference, August - December 2007 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Call Box Unveiling events and related email correspondence, and Submission Guidelines folder, May - December 2009 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Call Box Unveiling events and related email correspondence folder, January - April 2009 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Cherry Blossom Festival, Unveiling Call Box for ADA loose items, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- ADA Call Box information, Southwesters, call box project brochures, newspaper articles, and call box maps folder, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Cherry Blossom Festival, Southwester, SWNA Annual Reports (loose items), 2011 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- National Registry Registration Form, Public Hearing for Development of Waterfront, Correspondence, Correspondence and DC Heritage Project, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Cherry Blossom Festival, Conference DC, Call Box Map cards, Southwester issues, 2012 - 2013, 2015 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Southwester loose issues/"old copies", 1973 - 1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Southwester loose issues, 1976 - 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Southwester loose issues, 2008 - 2018 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Southwester loose issues, 2005 - 2012 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Southwester "early" issues binder, 1966 - 1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Southwester cardboard covers, 1980 - 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Southwester cardboard covers, 1985 - 1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Southwester cardboard covers, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Southwester cardboard covers, 1982 - 1984 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- SWNA Meeting Minutes binder, 2000 - 2005 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Articles of Incorporation - Southwest Community Council, List of Board Members, and Treasurer's Report, 1964 - 1968 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Southwesters Bound (7 items), 2001 - 2004 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Southwesters Bound (20 items), 1978 - 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Southwesters Bound (13 items), 1980 - 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Southwesters Bound (19 items) and SW Community Park booklet and Southwester Index, 1986 - 2005 (Box 13, Folder 1)